SALIH BEYATLI

FRONT END DEVELOPER

ICONTACT

Phone

+90 536 012 2667

Email

dev@salihbeyatli.com

Website

www.salihbeyatli.com

I SKILLS

Javascript (ES6+) Html Node.is Css

WordPress Bootstrap 5

Webflow

I PORTFOLIO

www www.salihbeyatli.com

Bē www.behance.net/salihbeyatli

www.github.com/salihbeyatli

ISOCIAL NETWORK

www.instagram.com/slh.bytl

in www.linkedin.com/in/salihbeyatlı

www.twitter.com/salihbeyatli

IINTEREST

Technology Art Architectural Space

Design

Game Development Software

ABOUT

"Hello, I'm Salih Beyatli. I am developing myself in the fields of frontend and UI / UX. I am an extremely creative and innovative web designer. I have a strong understanding of user experience and web standards. I aim to create responsive websites that are both userfriendly and visually appealing."

EXPERIENCE

2020-2021 Web Developer

Beyat Door

HTML - CSS - Javascript - WordPress

2020-2021 Graphic User Interface Designer

Cilka Door

HTML - CSS - UI/UX - Image Editing

2020-2021 Graphic Designer Internship

Deniz Media

Image Editing - Video Animation - Web Services -

Web Design - Graphic Design

■ CERTIFICITA

2022 Complete Applied Web Development

<u>Training - Udemy</u>

2022 Build Great Web Projects From Scratch

with Bootstrap 4 - Udemy

2022 <u>The Beginner Frontend Web Development</u>

Pathway - Patika.dev

■ EDUCATION

2016-2020 Kayseri Vocational and Technical

Anatolian High School

Bachelor degree

Web Design and Programming